at triangle we Implement business
Central Cloud to Spanish smbs with a
focus on the finance and supply chain
modules we were either focusing on
growing our team or we were focusing on
growing and helping our customers by
joining the BC res skill program we can
do both at the same time within the
program they're trained on product
training on professional skills and they
have onet toone Co in sessions the
product training is very extensive first
it's focus on the knowledge needed for
the business Central certification but
after that you go more in depth into
topics such as co-pilot and AI Advanced
Warehouse functionality Telemetry and so
on the program helps the seniors in my
company by giving them a piece of mind
that their team members have a solid
product knowledge the rescu program
helps our company to grow by Saving Time
to our lead team now we can be focused
on consultancy and our junior team has
the knowledge and also the confidence to
resolve the client issues by the
themselves the professional skills
training are all those skills the
Consultants need such as presentation
communication skills prees activities
but also negotiation skills and these
skills the soft skills really help you
put the consultant in front of the
customer in no time because of the
coaching in the program we really see
the professional develop velopment of
the team I think that the coaching and
the mentoring are a really core part of
the rescu program I feel really
appreciated of David he has helped me a
lot if I had any doubts or if I need to
ask him something he is always available
the best thing about the rku community
is that it brings a sense of belonging
not only you have peers that you can
create meaningful connections that can
sustain throughout your career but also
you get the best and cool training from
Microsoft there is a good quality and
variety of webinars workshops and the
good quality of the trainers now I don't
ask every time sergy everything that I
didn't know on business Central at this
early stage it is incredible I cannot
think of a better opportunity that I can
give to my team when I started that
triangle I started from the bottom I
didn't know anything about business
Central I didn't know even exist we have
what we've been asking for for Microsoft
for many years
we have an incredible program that not
only trains our people but helps us
bring new diverse people into our
community the more people using the res
skill program the bigger the chances of
making a big impact in our community and
changing the future of how we hire and
how we retain and who we are as a
community
[Music]